格兰特・威德克来电
已安装窃听器
疑犯追踪 第1季 第2集
2002年6月10日
2007年
89街和西区大道交界口
It's at 89th and West End.
安静  他来了  我知道
Just be quiet. He's coming. I know.
把电话给我
Give me your phone.
吧台后面那个家伙专为人解决麻烦
Guy behind the bar's a fixer.
拜托了
Please.
半小时后见  拜拜
Okay, see you in 30. Yeah, bye.
保镖实在是太多了
for a real estate developer.
被原油污染了
Ruined by an oil spill.
本月最佳软件工程师
Software engineer of the month.
比如说  和你同监室的
Like that brother of that gang leader
别
Don't...
别打给我  里瑟先生
Don't call me, mr. Reese.
别担心
Don't worry.
别管我
Just leave me alone.
别骗小孩子啊
You really shouldn't lie to kids.
别让我在周围看见你
Don't let me see you around here again.
别偷懒
Don't dawdle.
别拖到明年了
Sometime this year?
不  我不想  这就是问题所在
No, I don't. That's the whole point.
不  这只是纽约
No, that's just New York.
不  只是
No, it's--it's just...
不
No.
不不不  这太慢了  这边走
No, no, no. Too slow. Come on. This way.
不管你是被害人和行凶者  如果你的号码被列出来
But victim or perpetrator, if your number's up,
不好意思
Sorry.
不会有人再伤害你了
No one's gonna hurt you again.
不留姓名  现金结账
No names. Cash.
布鲁肯林的市民们应得的  先生
The good people of Brooklyn deserve it, sir.
不是
No.
不是你的
Not yours.
不想和你死了的哥哥说话吗
You don't want to talk to your dead brother?
不幸的是  子女不能挑父母
Unfortunately, you can't pick your parents.
不知道
I don't know.
No.
差点错过了
Almost missed it.
拆掉你的监控摄像头
dismantle your surveillance cameras
迟早
Sooner or later,
出现了一个男人
and this, uh, other gentleman
除掉所有能继承财产的人
Expected to clean up after it cleared probate.
除了滑轮的激情生活之外没别的
Nothing but attitude on wheels.
戳穿了西洋镜呢
say the wrong thing?
此次情况有些特别
this situation is somewhat unique.
此外  我还要更仔细地检查一遍
And I want to look at Grant Whitaker's finances
从那之后  他多次因店内行窃被捕
Since, he's been popped multiple times for shoplifting,
从你好哥们斯蒂尔斯身上顺来的
Took it off your friend Stills.
大隐隐于市
is in plain sight.
但戴夫说他被炒了
But Dave said he was laid off.
但监控录像上没有记录
But it's nothing on the surveillance cameras.
但如果机器是对的而且她确实还活着
But if the machine is right and she's still alive,
但说实话  我有点厌倦了
But, honestly, this is getting exhausting for me.
但他不接电话
But he's not answering.
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
但她说她很想念你
But she did mention how much she missed you.
但我不明白他们为什么还要追杀她
I'm just not sure why they're still coming after her.
但我不知道的是
But what I don't know
但我从没想过...
But I never-- I never thought
但我会找到他
but I'll find him.
但我们不知道特蕾莎还有多少时间
But we don't know how much time Theresa has left.
但我们得尽快查清
But we need to figure it out fast.
但我弄清楚她怎么维持生计了
But I did figure out how she's been providing for herself.
但我认识你  比尔
But I know you, Bill.
但我需要一个搭档
But I needed a partner.
但相信我  你并不想抛弃大家
But, trust me, you don't want to leave people behind.
但这机器不懂其中的区别
But a machine doesn't understand the difference
但这世上还有人爱着你
But you do have someone out there that loves you.
但政府干活都是这样
But, like everything with the government,
当然  你下个月就可以开始动工了
Hell, you can break ground as early as next month.
倒是合理的假设
That's a reasonable assumption.
得教会机器如何进行筛选  从电邮
You have to teach the machine to sift through the emails,
德雷克  还记得这地方吗
Remember this place, Derek?
德雷克  我们得谈谈
Yeah, Derek, we need to talk.
德雷克  我是在谈生意
I'm talking business, Derek.
德雷克  怎么了
What's the matter, Derek?
德雷克没能走出这种恐惧
Derek never came out of the funk.
的确不能解释
No, it wouldn't.
等等  快来
Just--just... - wait. Hurry up.
等等  这是谁
Wait a second. Who's this?
等等
Hold it.
Wait.
等我的信号
Wait for my signal.
迪肯・佩奇
Deacon Page.
电话没人听  也没有更新地址
No answer on the cell phone. No forwarding address.
定位信号在活跃状态
The GPS signal is active,
丢掉的东西找到了
都是单枪匹马  除了一项
in all his real estate deals except one.
对不起  公事缠身
Yeah, I'm sorry. I got tied up here at work.
对了  里瑟先生  我们按我的安排见面
And, Mr. Reese, we'll meet on my schedule.
对了  在他嘴里发现了这个
Oh, yeah. Found this stuffed in his mouth.
躲着你
From you.
而兰代尔想要独吞
And Landale wants it all.
而你却袖手旁观
And you did nothing?
而且一半都被改掉了
And half of them have been redacted.
而是为了保护所有人
We built it to save everybody.
而他现在有动作了
And he's walking.
而现在是由你在跟他们打交道吧
And now you're cutting a deal with him, aren't you?
而政府认为这些罪行无关紧要
Crimes the government considered irrelevant.
房间不错啊
Nice room.
风景不错
Nice spot.
弗斯科的线人告诉了我一个杀手
Fusco's C.I. pointed me towards
感谢致电纽约芬威旅店
Thank you for calling the Fenwick, New York.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
格兰特
Grant.
格兰特・威德克的财政状况
much more carefully.
格兰特打包票说  只要政府清理干净了
Grant swore that it was gonna be a ten-bagger
格兰特发誓说绿地会是一单大买卖
Grant, he swore that Greenpoint was gonna be the big one.
给你点关于夫妻相处的建议
Little relationship advice,
给你妻子买的吗
Those for your wife?
给我找特蕾莎・威德克
Name's Theresa Whitaker.
给再多的钱也不行
Not even if they paid me my quote.
根据警方记录
According to the police,
跟你说的一样
just like you said they'd be.
跟我以前送进去的那堆人渣作伴了
A whole cellblock of degenerates that I sent upstate.
雇他的人有可能发现
The people that hired him
哈罗德  你这朋友是谁
So who's your friend, Harold?
还没结果
Inconclusive.
还是个刺儿头呢
And, uh, kicking.
还是你让兰代尔的人干的
Or did you let Landale do it?
还隐蔽携带武器
Carrying a concealed weapon.
还有  我们又赢了一个奖项
And we won another award.
还有这个
And, uh, this.
孩子  你在这做什么
Sweetheart? What are you doing here?
好  我来处理  戴夫
Okay. I'll see what I can do, Dave.
好啊  莱奈尔
Hello, Lionel.
好吧  你说过  抱歉
You did. I'm sorry.
好伪装成抢劫闹出人命的样子
to make it look like a robbery gone wrong.
好消息是  这姑娘还活着
The good news, the girl is alive.
合伙购买了一些小地块
with the real estate holding company Landale.
和其它无关信息
and the ones that are irrelevant.
后来他们发现女孩还活着
'til they found out the girl was still alive.
回馈社会
give something back.
或许没死呢
Or maybe not.
或许他们雇了别人来收尾
Maybe they hired somebody new to finish the job.
或许她去找朋友了
Maybe she went to friends.
机器却能看见所有的一切
The machine sees almost everything.
吉米・卡霍尔
Jimmy Calhoun.
记得给我档案
Get me the file.
既然机器吐了她的号
Well, the machine did spit out her number,
继而留给了你  德雷克
And then to you, Derek.
监控摄像头
surveillance cameras...
监听电话和银行转账中
wire-tapped phones, bank transactions,
建造这栋奥威尔式的梦魇[《1984》作者]
in order to build this Orwellian nightmare.
警方已经结案终止调查了
The police have concluded their investigation.
警方只看到他们要找的东西
The police only see what they choose to look for.
就是被我用你的枪打死
The one I shot with your gun
就是说  像你这样的人
People like you, in other words.
就为了让他们还债
Just to get their money back out.
就这么走进去和他谈
who just walk into the joint.
卡霍尔  她父亲的生意伙伴
Calhoun, the father's business partner.
卡特警探
Detective Carter.
看看我能上哪儿雇到一个
Find out where I can hire one.
看来她很难信任别人
Seems she has some trust issues.
看来她是跟另一个比她大的破坏公物的小子一起被捕
Seems she was picked up with an older boy for vandalism,
看来我们得见面好好聊聊了
It's time we sat down face to face.
看来我能赚积分哦
Guess I can use the miles.
看上去是合法的
It all looked legit.
看着点  猪头
Watch it, idiot!
可还不能解释为什么你有私人护卫
But it doesn't quite explain the private security,
可能得要你帮忙啊  芬奇
Might need a little help, Finch.
可有些女人
But some women,
肯定会引起反对  他们就会关掉它
There'd be such an outcry. They'd turn it off.
恐怖分子不会就那么站在街角
Terrorists don't exactly stand out on street corners, you know?
快点
Come on. Go. Go.
快关灯
Quick. Turn 'em all off.
快去
Get moving.
快走
Let's go.
莱奈尔  你在担心我吗
Lionel, you worried about me?
兰代尔  把地址发给我
Landale. Send me the address.
兰代尔财务公司  在二楼
Landale Financials, second floor.
兰代尔公司的卡霍尔
Calhoun. Landale.
兰代尔却要马上收债
Landale wanted their money immediately.
兰代尔也牵涉在内
Landale's involved.
老板是个叫卡霍尔的人
Principal is a guy named Calhoun.
老地方
Usual place.
离特蕾莎・威德克远点
Theresa Whitaker. Right now.
里瑟先生  想必你也清楚
The best place to hide, Mr. Reese, as you well know,
利用电话地址数据和脸部识别技术
using cell phone location data, facial recognition.
联调局  这家伙你动不了  卡特
Feds. This one's above your pay grade, Carter.
连我自己都不想知道
I'd rather I didn't know myself.
联系方式吗
For your ex-husband, do you?
两个杀手伺机杀一个人
Two hit men were waiting to kill a guy,
两年前发生在博瑞湾的谋杀案
Two-year-old murder-suicide out in Bowery Bay.
邻居报的警
Neighbor called it in.
旅店的工作人员说
Hotel staff said they might have seen
绿地  布鲁克林外的那块地
Greenpoint, bunch of land out in Brooklyn
玛姬说他被调走了
Maggie said he'd been transferred,
没  但是我刚找到我们要找的人
No, but I think I just found our guy.
没关系  我能理解
Not at all. I can only imagine.
没见到特蕾莎吗
No sign of Theresa?
没有  当然没有
No. Of course not.
没有  我们分居之后就很少联系了
No, we've barely spoken since we split.
没有
No kids.
没准你就在哪见过她  长官
Maybe you seen her around, chief.
没准他是个尚在恢复阶段的外交家
Well, maybe he's a recovering diplomat.
每个人
Everyone.
每个人的电邮  每通电话
That's every email, every phone call,
每天午夜
Every night at midnight,
名叫索尼克
a contract killer named Solnick.
某个我只见过一次的人
Some guy I met one time.
某个小朋友或许知道她在哪
Who might know her whereabouts.
目标是谁
What's the name?
哪位
Who is this?
那个黑帮老大的兄弟
that lives on your cell block.
那个有钱人正要回家
This rich guy was on his way home,
那孩子握着价值连城的遗产  芬奇
Kid's worth a fortune, Finch.
那好
Good.
那么说来特蕾莎・威德克没去找亲人
So if Theresa didn't go to family,
那你又怎么知道
and you know that how?
那女孩在哪儿
Where's the girl?
那女孩子挂了  还我手机
That girl's gone. Give me back my phone.
那是两年前  她父亲格兰特
Two years ago, her father Grant
那是两年前的事了
Two years ago.
那她为什麽到现在还不露面
Then why hasn't she shown up by now?
那她一定是卷入了什么事
so she must be caught up in something.
那谈谈你杀的其他人吧
How about some of the other people you killed?
那条船上究竟发生了什么
what happened to those people on that boat.
那为什么凶手没有杀掉特蕾莎
So why didn't the shooter kill Theresa?
那我就能跟踪到她了
I might be able to track her down.
那我就闲话少说了
I'll make it quick, then.
那我们要找一个鬼魂吗
So we're looking for a ghost?
那种经历实在太可怕了
It was a pretty traumatic experience.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
能不能找到就看运气了
Good luck tracking him down.
你把他们扔进了博瑞湾
then dumped in the Bowery Bay.
你不来吗
You coming?
你不能杀我
You can't kill me.
你不是凶案组的吗
Aren't you homicide?
你从消防梯下去
Fire escape. You can go down.
你打算什么时候才告诉我
When were you going to tell me?
你到底是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
你得赶上进度啊
You--you got to keep up.
你得加快点速度  好吗
we're gonna need it a little faster, okay?
你得去信任别人
You're gonna have to trust someone.
你的扳机狂人流浪汉又来了  卡特
Your trigger happy hobo, Carter.
你的机器又吐号了吗
Your machine kick out another number?
你对此事的大力支持与耐心
Can't tell you how much
你该去休息一下
You should get some rest.
你高估了自己在整件事中的价值
You have vastly overestimated your value in this process.
你告诉她我的事了吗
You tell her about me?
你哥哥格兰特做的那笔生意
That deal your brother Grant made,
你跟德雷克有没有小孩
Did you and Derek have any children?
你跟我一样
You're like me.
你好  哈罗德
Hi, Harold.
你好  我叫亚瑟・百灵爵  自由国相互保险公司
Hello. Arthur Bellinger, Liberty State Mutual.
你好
Hello.
你和你妻子之间出了点问题
You and your wife are having some problems.
你和你先生德雷克是列作近亲对不对
You and your husband Derek are listed as next of kin?
你和他们设计害了你哥哥
And you set your brother up with them.
你家人的悲剧已经无法改变了
You know, there's no changing what happened to your family.
你看上去不像个坏人  比尔
Now, you don't seem like a bad guy, Bill.
你可得想清楚了
you need to think it through.
你可真是出了大力
You really turned this thing around,
你没法告诉我
About how this man looks?
你没有联系方式吗
You got no contact info?
你没有你前夫的
You don't have any contact information
你妻子不是喜欢玫瑰吗
I thought your wife liked roses.
你确定我们能拿下这块地皮吗
You're sure we're free and clear on this?
你确实帮了他
You helped him, all right.
你确实不干净  莱奈尔
That's because you are dirty, Lionel.
你什么意思  变态玩笑么
What is this? Some kind of sick joke?
你是卡特警探吗
Are you detective Carter?
你是谁
Who are you?
Who is this?
你是怎么进来的
How the hell'd you get in here?
你说过你想做出一些改变
Said you wanted to make a difference,
你说什么
Excuse me.
你为什么放了那个小姑娘
is why you let the girl live.
你先把我的内务部档案拿走先
Yeah. Right after you pull my I.A.D. File.
你想扮演上帝  这就是你的意图吗
You want to play god? Is that the deal?
你需要能相信的人
You're gonna need to trust someone.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
你已经都清楚了
You already know.
你以前见过他吗
you ever see him before?
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
你有准备告诉我是什么理由吗
Are you ever gonna tell me those reasons?
你在胡说什么啊
What are you talking about?
你在哪
Where are you?
你在受到监视
You are being watched.
你在找哈罗德吗
Are you looking for harold?
你在这儿工作吗
Do you work here?
你真该长个眼睛看看路
You really need to watch where you're going.
你知道
You knew...
你知道是谁杀了你全家吗
Do you have any idea who targeted your family?
你知道我们在这儿造什么
You knew what we were building here.
你知道我跑不过你
You know I can't keep up with you.
你知道我是谁  你到底想不想谈
You know who. You want to meet me or not?
你总得学会去信任别人
Well, you're gonna need to trust someone at some point.
你最后一次见这个女孩子是什么时候  迪肯
Want to know the last time you seen this girl, Deacon.
你最近一直在打听我啊
You been asking a lot of questions about me.
你昨天去了兰代尔财务公司
Landale Financial, where you were yesterday.
您不满意吗
You weren't satisfied?
弄到一个名字
Got a name.
期待着了  吉姆
Look forward to it, Jim.
前夫
Ex-husband.
枪口印痕是事后伪造的
Muzzle impressions were made after the fact,
强制配对
成功
-请进  -谢谢
- Come in.  - Thank you.
请问有什么事
How can I assist you?
去你的吧
Kiss my ass.
去年就生效了
The divorce went through last year.
全国范围内吗
In the country?
全家人一去不回
No one comes home.
却只被提拔过两次
Only been promoted twice.
然后吞枪自杀
Then turned the gun on himself.
让人惊奇的是  格兰特是对的
You know, the kicker is that Grant was right.
让他早早地就进坟墓了
Right into an early grave. With no will.
如果被别人发现了
If anyone else ever found out,
如果你要离开你的妻子
if you're gonna step out on your wife,
如果是的话  你被解雇了
Because if you do, you're fired.
如果她要在网上出售卡的信息
If she tries to sell these online,
如果这个女孩的号码出现了
If the girl's number has come up,
杀了你全家的人已经进了监狱
The man that killed your family's in jail.
杀小孩的人在监狱里可不受欢迎
Guys who kill kids aren't popular in jail.
上车
Get in the truck.
上次你割得好狠啊
You got me pretty good back there.
上周  我们监室的一个小混混
Had some punk on my cell block last week
婶婶没问题  叔叔失踪了
Aunt's fine. Uncle's M.I.A.
甚至还坚持支付人寿保险的保金
Even kept up payments on life insurance.
失踪
M.I.A.?
十分重要  三倍报酬
High priority. Triple your usual fee.
十五岁
15 years old.
使之看起来像是近距离击杀
Made it look point blank,
是
Yes?
是啊  感谢那些警惕的邻居哈
Yeah, thank goodness for vigilant neighbors, huh?
是啊
Uh, yes.
市场崩盘
Market crashed.
-是的  -你觉得呢
- Yeah. - You think?
是的
It is.
Yes.
似乎你在这里工作了17年了
Seems you've worked here for 17 years.
是吗  你才不懂
Yeah? What do you know?
是你亲自雇的杀手
Did you hire the hit man yourself,
是谁杀了她全家  以及为什么
who killed her family and why.
是我
Hey, it's me.
是我就这么干
That's how I would have done it.
收到
Copy that.
收件人: 特蕾莎
有条子你快闪
手头有近3000万美金
30 million or so in holdings.
谁雇的你
Who hired you to do it?
说
Go.
说他们听到了争吵
Thought they heard a dispute.
说他听说了我的所作所为
say he heard I did.
说有两个人要杀他
said a couple of guys tried to kill him,
搜索特蕾莎・威德克
Stop searching for Theresa?
索尼克是在维护自己的尊严
Solnick's been defending his honor.
所以
So.
所以叫人杀了他全家
Killed the whole family.
所以那个男人长什么样
So you can't tell me anything
所以你教它分辨二者
So you taught it the difference?
所以你没去投靠他
Is that why you didn't come to him?
所以他们把他一家都揪了出来
So they took him out along with everyone in his family.
所以他们才继续追杀她
So that's why they're still coming after her.
所以他们才没杀我
That's the only reason why they didn't kill me.
所以我安排了一次探访
So I've arranged a visit.
所以我告诉他我认得这些人
So I told him I know these guys.
所以我完全无需向你解释
Then I don't have to explain to you
所有这些人
All these people.
她把这个装在自动取款机上
She left this at an ATM machine.
他大概会知道是谁干的
he might know who did it.
他的14处地产都赔了本
He was upside down on 14 properties.
他都没道别
He didn't even say goodbye.
她父亲买下的地皮价格翻了五十倍
Land the father bought panned out fifty fold.
她还给我看了张老照片
She even showed me an old photo.
她还活着
She's alive.
她和她的家人都被杀害了
She was murdered, along with the rest of her family.
他和一家名叫兰代尔的地产公司
He bought a couple of parcels of land
它会删除所有无关信息
It deletes the irrelevant list.
他会在这儿陪着你
and he's gonna stay with you.
他会照顾好你
He'll take care of you.
他会做这种事情
That he would do anything like this.
她家老头把自己全家都给做了
Old man went postal on her whole family.
他开枪打死了妻子儿女
He shot his wife and kids,
它看到了与普通人相关的暴力罪行
Violent crimes involving ordinary people.
她可能在周围的房子里
Maybe she's in one of the surrounding buildings.
她肯定还活着
She must be alive.
他肯定很想听听他兄弟的临终遗言
I'm sure he'd love to know his brother's last words.
他来了  芬奇  快离开那儿
He's coming, Finch. Get off that floor.
他来了  他就在门外
He's coming. He's right outside the door.
他来了
He's here.
它没法分辨危及国家安全的罪行
between those crimes that are relevant to national security
他没有杀掉特蕾莎
may have found out he didn't kill Theresa.
他们不肯作为  所以我决定插手
They wouldn't act, so I decided I would.
他们撤掉了整个档案
They pulled the whole file.
他们好像看到两个人上去
Two people coming and going,
她们或许会雇两个人来你办公室
they might just hire a couple of guys to come to your office,
他们或许知道威家到底面卷入了什么麻烦
They might know what kind of trouble Whitaker was in.
他们揪着我不放  就差把我送去上城区
'cause they got me one step from fighting off
他们全都不知
None of them.
他们让我继承遗产
They made me the administer of probate.
他们认为我不干净
They think I'm dirty.
他们说海浪或许卷走了她的遗体
They--they said that the current would have taken her body,
他们需要我
They need me.
他们只需要再雇几个律师就行了
They'll just hire another couple of lawyers.
它能偷取账号和密码
It captures account numbers and pins.
她人似乎很好
She seems like a lovely person.
他是房地产开发商
He was a real estate developer.
她是用的无线网吗
Is it a wireless network?
他说这都怪德雷克
He said it was Derek's fault.
她死了
She's dead.
他想和你聊聊
He wants to talk to you.
他沿着走廊走过来
He's coming down the hall.
他要切断走廊的灯
He's gonna cut out the lights in the hallway.
她也活不久了
She won't be for long.
她叔叔有一大堆债主要躲
Her uncle's hiding from a dozen different creditors,
他已经过去了
It's done. It's already done.
他又请假了吗
Is he taking another personal day?
他在被枪杀前的遗言
Before that man put a bullet in his head,
他在这里干什么
Why would he turn up here?
-他找你麻烦  -怎么回事啊  哥们
- Is he riding you?  - What's up with that, man?
他只是不够钱买下整块地皮
He just didn't have enough to cover all the parcels.
他走向了保险盒
He's going for the fuse box.
太迟了
It's too-- it's too late.
谈谈格兰特遗产的查验
Something about grant's assets coming out of probate.
特蕾莎  等等
Wait. Theresa.
特蕾莎  你现在能信任我了吗
Theresa. Are you gonna trust me now?
特蕾莎  这位是哈罗德
Theresa, this is Harold,
特蕾莎
Theresa.
特蕾莎...你胡说些什么啊
Theres--what are you talking about?
特蕾莎・威德克封掉的少年犯罪记录上写着
Sealed juvie record on Theresa.
特蕾莎不能一个人留在这儿
Theresa can't be left alone here.
特蕾莎的遗体一直未被找到
Theresa's body was never recovered.
特蕾莎是法定的继承人
Theresa is the legal heir to that property.
特蕾莎是个很聪明的孩子
Smart as a whip, Theresa.
特蕾莎也是  挂了
So's theresa. Got to go.
特蕾莎正在网上出售那些账号
Theresa just tried to sell those account numbers online.
天生的坏蛋
A genuine bad guy.
调查进行的如何了
How did your research go?
条子看漏了
Cops missed it.
听好  你有困难我不管
Look, your predicament is not my doing or my concern.
听我说
Listen to me.
听着  你在弄的那个数据库
Listen, um, that database you're coding,
通知你的走狗
Call off the dogs.
同时  我们还得弄清楚
In the meantime, we need to figure out
推定死亡
Uh, "Presumed dead"?
威德克
格兰特  生于1963  蕾切尔  生于  1967
马修  生于1991  特蕾莎生于1996
威德克在他的所有投资中
Whitaker was sole investor
为什么
And how's that?
Why?
为什么这么在意一个十几岁的孩子
Why are they so worried about a teenager?
喂  他可不喜欢别人
Hey, he don't talk to people
喂
Hello?
Yeah.
问题是索尼克因为另一桩案子被关起来了
Problem is solnick got himself locked up for a separate job,
我把你电话告诉他了
I gave him your cell.
我不会丢下你
I'm staying with you.
我不会杀一个小姑娘
I wouldn't have killed the girl.
我不会允许
'cause I won't let them.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我不认识你
I don't know you.
我不杀小孩子
I don't kill kids.
我不是来找你麻烦的
Not--not looking for a rematch.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
我猜猜  穿西装的人吧
Let me guess. Some guy in a suit.
我尝试过帮格兰特一把
I tried to help Grant.
-我处理好了  -很好
- I took care of it. - Good.
我从基础开始做起
I'm starting with the basics here.
我从没想过伤害任何人
I never meant for anyone to get hurt.
我带礼物来了  威士忌
I come bearing gifts. Whisky.
我待她视同己出
I loved her like she was my own daughter.
我倒是查到了点线索
I got a lead on another kid
我得去跟我在局子里的朋友谈谈了
I'll have to talk to my friend in the department.
我得一个人走
You have to go without me.
我的律师又不干了吗
Did my lawyer quit again?
我对分工十分满意
I'm perfectly happy with the division of labor.
我刚还觉得
And here I was thinking
我刚看见了特蕾莎的叔叔德雷克
I think I just found Theresa's uncle Derek.
我告诉她  一旦有人知道她还活着
I told her anyone ever knew she was alive,
我给机器设了程序
I've coded the machine.
我给你叫了客房服务
Ordered you room service.
我给你留了几条留言
I left you a couple messages
我跟丢了她
I, uh, I lost her.
我跟你说过  里瑟先生
As I told you, Mr. Reese,
我跟他说了一样的话
I told him the same thing.
我过不去
I can't get through there.
我还指望着能把她带回家
And I was hoping that maybe it would bring her home.
我好感动
I'm touched.
我很抱歉  这引起了一段很不愉快的回忆
I'm sorry. This is just drudging up some really difficult memories.
我很惊讶我的大伯
I'm surprised my brother-in-law
我会打给你
I'll call you.
我会通知你去哪
I'll let you know where to go.
我会知道  因为它是我造的
I know because...I built it.
我觉得不是  我还指望你知道
I don't think so. I was hoping you knew.
我觉得不是
I don't think so.
我就不得不来收尾
I'd finish the job.
我就猜你还在这儿
I thought you might still be here.
我就是没法相信居然会变成这样
I just can't believe that it came to this.
我就说我们得离开这
I told you we should have left.
我就要进入下一个问题了
I'm almost ready to move on to the next problem.
我看见他了
I can see him.
我来帮你
I'm here to help you.
我来开车
I'll drive.
我来问问你
Let me ask you this.
我勒个...
What the--?
我了解失去亲人的感受
I know what it's like to lose someone.
我没跟他们说我们裁掉一半员工
I didn't tell them that we laid off half the staff
我们不必知道
Well, we don't have to.
我们得查出这女孩是谁
We got to find out who this girl is.
我们得快走
We have to go. Now.
我们负责格兰特・威德克先生的人寿保险单
We wrote the term life policies for Grant Whitaker.
我们感激不尽  议员先生
We appreciate your patience and support on this, councilman.
我们建造它  是为了阻止恐怖分子
We built it to stop terrorists before they could act.
我们就会找到你
we'll find you.
我们埋的是付空棺木
We buried an empty coffin.
我们没时间了
We haven't got much time.
我们晚点得见个面
We need to meet later.
我们要做什么
What are we doing?
我们一起去吃顿饭怎么样
I was thinking we could grab a bite, okay?
我们造这台机器不是为了保护某个人
We didn't build this to save somebody.
我们怎么能这样苟活啊
knowing that someone out there needs help?
我们知道他们有经济上的困难
We knew they were having, uh, financial issues,
我明白了
I get it.
我能问下你要去哪儿吗
Can I ask you where you're going?
我朋友说我可以信任你
My friend said I could trust you.
我期待你的发现
I'll be interested to hear what you discover.
我侵入了她叔叔的手机账户
I hack the uncle's cell phone account.
我去拜访了你婶婶伊丽莎白
You know, I went to see your Aunt Elizabeth.
我去给董事会拍马  我去兑现支票
I schmooze the board, I cash out the checks,
我去领奖  你干大部分的活
I pick up the awards. You do most of the work.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
我是卡特
Yeah. Carter.
我是说  她的遗体
Her body, I mean?
我手上有八件案子涉及到他的指纹
I've got eight case files connected to this guy's prints,
我说过我很注重隐私
I told you I'm a very private person.
我完全不记得了
I don't remember much at all.
我下周得签字把地皮交给他们
I'm supposed to sign it over to 'em next week.
我想和你谈谈你杀掉的那一家人
I'd like to talk to you about that family you murdered,
我想去做点调查
Thought I'd do a little research.
我需要这案子的警方报告
I'll need a police report on this.
我压根没打算告诉你
I wasn't gonna tell you, I guess.
我要把这个项目交给你
I got to hand it to you.
我要你给我找份文件
I need you to pull a file for me.
我要你和哈罗德待在一块儿
I need you to stay here with Harold.
我要去拜访一个人
I'm gonna pay a man a visit.
我要去查查那个杀手
And I'm gonna look into the shooter.
我要是你就报警  再找个好离婚律师
I would call the police and a good divorce lawyer.
我也不知
I don't know.
我有他旧的手机号码
I have a--an old cell phone number.
我有我的理由
I have my reasons.
我在监视他
I've got eyes on him.
我在哪能找到她
Where can I find her?
我在人力资源部作了一番调查
I did some digging down in H.R.
我再问你一次
I'll ask you one more time.
我在追踪她登录的IP地址
I'm tracing the IP address where she logged on.
我找到了那个婶婶和叔叔
I've tracked down a recent address
我这儿没尸体
I don't have any cold ones for you.
我这就去
I'm on my way.
我这里有线索了
Oh, I think I may have a lead.
我知道你们家的遭遇
I know what happened to you and your family.
我知道我们说好了
Look, I know our deal.
我转遍了城里所有的滑板小子去的公园
I've been to every skate-rat park in the city.
我自作主张订了四间
Took the liberty of booking all four.
我最好把这个收起来
I better take this.
我最好一个人行动
I'm better off alone.
无关信息
Irrelevant?
无穷无尽的资金
the unlimited funds.
五十块钱的芝士汉堡
It's a $50 cheeseburger.
下一个问题是什么
What's the next problem?
现在的价值比当初翻了二三十倍
Now it's worth 20, 30 times what they put into it.
现在我连婶婶都不是了
Now I'm not even an aunt.
想让它学会如何追踪人
I'm trying to teach it to track people
向警方或者家属报到
With the police or a relative?
像你一样的普通人
People like you.
像是那个父亲干的
Like the father did it.
像喂鱼一样扔进水里
In the water like chum.
小心点
Be careful.
小心碰到头  卡霍尔先生
Watch your head, Mr. Calhoun.
携家人周末乘船出航
takes the family for a weekend sail.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
新闻头条啊  长官
News flash, chief.
信任  对我来说可不那么容易
Trust? That's not something I come by very easily.
要杀他们
Kill them.
要是你当初站出来  还你哥哥清白
If you'd come forward, cleared your brother's name,
要是我说话声音太大
And if I speak too loudly,
也解释不了为什么她至今未在别处出现
Or why she hasn't shown up anywhere else.
也理解隐姓埋名的感受
And to feel the need to disappear.
也是个杀手
A killer.
一个有能力介入其中的人
Someone with the skills to intervene.
伊丽莎白・威德克吗
Elizabeth Whitaker?
一台每时每刻都在监视你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
一直如此
Always have been.
已经成功阻止了许多恐怖计划
has already foiled a half dozen major terrorist plots.
因为不是他做的
that's because he didn't.
因为受当局的追捕  我们只能秘密合作
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
因为特蕾莎・威德克应该躺在这
You see, Theresa Whitaker should be right here.
因为这是桩雇凶杀人案
'cause this was a hit for hire,
应该说我更像独立承包商
I'm more like an independent contractor.
用你的信用卡
Your card.
用他的话说  "插手"了
quote "intervened," unquote.
有的人会被炒鱿鱼
Some would be fired.
有的人会被重新安排  获得提升
Some would be reassigned, promoted.
有个活给你干
I've got a job for you.
有个卖保险的来问了几个问题
about the insurance guy who came by, asking questions.
有个问题不得不问
I have to ask this.
有其他人在帮你吗
Was there anyone else helping you?
有人想害他们
That someone wanted to harm them.
有什么枪手的信息
What do we know about the shooter?
有时生活中的人就这么没了
Sometimes you just lose people.
有双重身份的人
Living double lives.
有些不服管教  但总的来说是个好孩子
Some disciplinary trouble, but basically a good kid.
有些女人会离开你就算了
Well, some women would just leave you.
又被你扔到牡蛎湾里的那位
Before you buried him out in Oyster Bay.
又来了  07年的失踪人口案
Here we go. Missing persons '07.
又是你
You. Again.
又是谁雇的你
Who hired you?
又有人要被卷入一起罪案了吗
Somebody else is gonna be involved in a crime?
于是那块地成了他的遗产
Which means that land goes into probate,
在公园里滑板罚款两百
$200 fine to skate in the park.
在洗衣店追杀你的那个人
The man who came after you at the laundry mat,
再有四五年吧
Four, five more years.
咱俩的关系更进一步了呢  哈罗德
We were getting a little closer, Harold.
早安  芬奇
Good morning, Finch.
早上好  哈罗德
Morning, Harold.
怎么  不想谈这一桩案子吗
What, you don't want to talk about that one?
怎么查
How?
怎么回事啊你  傻逼
What's your problem, fool?
找到有所隐瞒的人
looking for people that are hiding something,
找的是恶意的蓄谋
It looks for malicious intent.
这部分我也解释不通
That part I can't explain,
这城里大多数的雇凶杀人他都要抽头
Takes a piece of most contract killings in the city.
这次的号码是个叫特蕾莎・威德克的女孩
The number we've received is for a girl named Theresa Whitaker.
这次有些不同
This one is somewhat unusual.
这该死的机器知道的事
And this damn machine knew.
这个先放一边
That's gonna have to wait.
这和你无关
No thanks to you.
这很常见
It happens.
这会用多长时间
How long will this take?
这机器所提供的情报
The intelligence the machine produces
这机器找的是搞阴谋的人
This thing looks for plotters, for schemers.
这家伙危险的很
This guy's as dangerous as they get.
这就是...
So this is...
这可是个转折点
This is a real game-changer.
这块地就能卖出天价
as soon as the government cleaned up the site.
这里很安全
You're safe here.
这里面说他们的遗体都被找到了
Says here they found the bodies.
这里是他们扔下你哥哥一家的地方
Where they dumped your brother's whole family
这两个人就是打不了高尔夫了而已
Just a couple of guys ain't ever gonna play golf again.
这两年来她就不用躲着了
she might not have spent the last two years hiding.
这涉及到正在调查的案件
Yeah, it's part of an ongoing investigation.
这是不是意味着他们会停止
Does this mean that they're gonna
这是次很专业的谋杀
This was a professional hit.
这是个盗卡器
It's a skimmer.
这事跟你叔叔德雷克有关吗
Did it have anything to do with your Uncle Derek?
这是人道主义贡献奖
This is for services to humanity.
这世上只有八个人
There are exactly eight people in the world
这是我爸爸说的
What my dad said,
这是政府的监控数据吗
Is this is the government feeds?
这些人中有多少知道其实你拥有整个公司
So how many of these people know you own the entire company?
这样更安全
It's safer.
这样就能看到我们房间里的光
He's gonna see the lights in our room.
这样没用
This isn't gonna work.
这又是什么奖
What's this one for?
这只是一笔脏钱的幌子
It was a front for dirty money.
这种涉及到冗长繁琐法律调查的个案
In cases like this involving prolonged legal investigation,
这桩灭门案的事情
If someone did wipe out the family,
真没想到啊
Not exactly what I expected.
真让人刮目相看
That's very impressive.
真希望他能去寻求帮助
Wish he would have reached out.
真希望他早点来找我
Wish that he would have... come to me.
争吵
A dispute.
整个部门会被解散
The entire department could be overhauled.
整理信息
Sorting them all out.
政府来了  把这块地清理干净了
Government came through. They cleaned up the site.
政府有一套秘密的系统
The government has a secret system--
只不过他现在是穿西装的杀手
Only now he's a killer in a suit.
知道吗
See...
知道是谁雇的杀手吗
Do we know who ordered the hit?
知道有那么多人需要帮助  却袖手傍观
How are we supposed to live with this,
知道这机器的存在
that know that this thing exists.
只有夫妇和18岁的儿子
Just the parents and the 18-year-old son.
直接来自米德堡的国家安全局
Direct from NSA at Fort Meade.
重新划分为住宅区
Rezoned for residential.
追踪来源
总不能让这块地荒废着啊
Saw what nobody else did on the property.
总是多花时间才能彻底结案
It can take some time to settle out.
总是磨磨蹭蹭
It took too damn long.
总之  回我电话吧
Anyway, call me back please.
走吧
Let's go.
最好跟他说是跟钱有关
You might want to mention that there's money involved.
最好找到她
Better find her.
最后见到活着的特蕾莎・威德克就是在这
This is the last place Theresa Whitaker was seen alive.
最新的在布鲁克林高地的地址
For the aunt and uncle in Brooklyn Heights.
昨晚没什么麻烦
No problems last night.
作为一个房产开发商
Well, Calhoun's got a lot of security